My experience during the internship in company "EXLRT" is very very positive, almost ideal.

I have learned a lot of new technologies that were not available to me during my strudies at faculty,
to be honest I didn't heard for 'SDL Tridion' never before but I was excited to learn it.

Also I have hardened and sharpened my old skills and knowlege.

Working environment in company is very good, colegues are good, talkative and from time to time they said some funny 
joke that made day better to everyone, but at the same time all of them are professionals who do they job best.

Previously mentioned is very important to me because I can not work normally and productive in harsh and 
tense environment.

Food and drink in canteen is always available (free of charge to interns) and I am also very satisfied with that
because it is very hard when you are student from far away village with limited budget that saves its money for 
home-work traveling. ( By the way ice cream was delicious desert on this hot weather :) )

Company provided me with laptop that made my programming life a lot easier, this gains on weight when if I tell
you than I dont have my own mobile PC.

Talking about training that I was attending, it was hard but slowely day by day I figured out how to solve problems
that mentor gave me.

But it would be much harder without Dušan Jovanović and Danilo Marić who helped me a lot to push further in my atempts
to progress in my assignments.

Stefan Klašnić was very good mentor, he was giving us guidelines how to solve problems and helped us when we were
stuck with some tasks and explained to us how things work.

When we got tired and exausted of work we would play some ping-pong that usually gave us motivation 
and energy to work further and also it gave us opportunity to better know each other and work together. 

Like I said at the begining, overall I am very satisfied and I would like to work in such a good company.

 








